- Daylight savings time not adjusting in calendar/reports

- Report needs FormatDate format

- Reminders sorted as strings not dates, 12/ comes after 1/

test all apps, all functions

	Address
		Add
		Modify
		Delete

	Appointment
		Add
		Modify
		Delete

	Customers 
		Add
		Modify
		Delete

test dst - report/appointment/calender
test validations better








NOTE: This message can be displayed again through any menu in the application by clicking the 'Help' menu option. (except the login page so read the next line to get that) 

----(Rubric A) Login Page

	○ The app will open into the login screen. You may login as anyone, but to test all features in the best possible manner you should login 
	  as Dunder Mifflin's best paper salesman, Jim Halpert (username: jhalpert / password: pam).
	○ The custom login page language is French - fr-fr. The apps native language is English.

----(Rubric B) Add/Update/Delete customer records including name/address/phone number

	○ You can launch the add/modify customers screen from the Customers menu option in any application or by clicking the 
	  chevrons to the right of the Customer ID field in the Appointments screen.

		○ Customers can only be deleted if they are not in use in other records.

	○ You can launch the add/modify addresses screen from the Addresses menu option in any application or by clicking the 
	  chevrons to the right of the Address ID field in the Customers screen.

		○ Addresses can only be deleted if they are not in use in other records.
		○ Addresses can only be modified if they are not in use in other records.

----(Rubric D) Calendar - View by Week and Month

	○ The app will open into the users calendar view, showing your appointments for January. You can change the view to weekly by clicking the 'by week' option button near the bottom of the page.
	○ From here, you can use the menu at the top to navigate to the different areas of the application or you can double click on an appointment in the gridview to open the appointment.

----(Rubric C) Appointments

	○ Appointments can be added / modified and deleted through this screen and can be accessed from the menu, or by double clicking any appointment in the calendar screens gridview.

----(Rubric E) Time Zone / DST support
	
	○ As per the instructions in the course FAQ, the app will pick up the Windows timezone and DST settings and automatically adjust all dates in the application to be representative  of your 
 	  selected time zone. 
	○ All example appointments written with business hours of (UTC-07:00) Arizona in context, which doesnt use daylight savings time.
	○ Time in the database is assumed to be UTC and all reads and writes are made using UTC.

----(Rubric F) Exception controls

	○ Many layers of validation are baked into the application, including but not limited to:
			
		○ Scheduling an appointment outside business hours / Scheduling overlapping appointments
		○ Entering nonexistent or invalid customer data / Entering an incorrect username and password
		○ SQL exception handling / Common sense date logic dates cant start after they end, cant start in the past, etc...
		○ Cannot delete/modify in use customers / Cannot delete/modify in use addresses
		○ Phone numbers must meet the following formats: 123-456-7890 / (123)456-7890 / 123 456 7890 / 123.456.7890 / + 91(123) 456-7890 / 1234567890
		○ Postal codes must be 5(85308) or 5-4(85308-1234) formats.
	
	○ Exceptions are thrown and field hovertips are implemented to explain what is wrong when bad choices are made.

----(Rubric G) Lambdas

	○There are 37 lambda functions sprinkled throughout the code, most of them are used with LINQ to query data.

	○ One of the more interesting ones is in SharedUtils.cs lines 404 and 414 and are part of a function that recieves a generic input. Reflection is used inside of a lambda expression to determine 
	 the generic inputs class name and to use different fields depending on the type.
	
	○ Also, line 471 in FrmAppointments.cs is an example where a multi-condition lambda expression is with LINQ to determine if there are any overlaps in appointments.

----(Rubric H) Reminders

	○ Once you login, in the background, your reminders will appear 15 minutes prior to the start date/time of any of your appointments in any screen in the application that your have navigated to. 
	○ To test this, you will have to add a new appointment or update an existing appointment to have a start date/time of 16 minutes past the current date/time in your local time zone, between the 
	  business hours of 8 and 5. 
	○ Once you save, wait 1 minute and the reminder will appear from any screen you've navigated into.

----(Rubric I) Reports
	
	○ All required reports can be viewed from the reports menu option.

----(Rubric J) Logging

	○ Login.txt is located in scheduler/RobertOgden-C969/bin/debug - as per the instruction, each login attempt (pass or fail) is tracked in this file.

----(Rubric K) - Professionalism

	○ I hope you enjoyed the application and code! Thank you!